

Jack Dennis

Full stack Software Engineer

PROFILE

I am a senior full stack software engineer and have over 8 years of experience in web and Mobile app design and development. I have mastered JavaScript and its frameworks like as React/Next, Vue/Nuxt, TypeScript, Node, express and have good eves in modern website design. Fast communication + best quality. Backend Frameworks: Laravel, Django

Other skills

services: Amazon Web Service, Google Cloud 9/2018-4/2021

Tools: Docker, Jira

CONTACT

Skype: live:.cid.2672397ca599ed27 EMAIL: bluedream0801@gmail.com Telegram: https://t.me/reliable1234

HOBBIES

Badminton Ping-Pong reading

EDUCATION

Nanyang Technical University

9/2010 - 10/2013

- -Specialized in Computer science
- -Major: Computer programming
- -Degree: Master's degree

WORK EXPERIENCE

IBM (Front end application developer)

2/2015-7/2017

- -Worked for IBM for 3 years
- -Build web application using React. is and integrated several APIs -role: designer, developer, manager

-salary: \$6000/month

Ambitious people group (JavaScript developer)

- -worked for 4 years
- -several kinds of software development Tracking solution, Cloud/IoT based Projects
- -JavaScript, React, TypeScript, AWS, IoT,
- -salary: \$6500 -8000/month

Upwork (Full stack Software Engineer)

7/2021-4/2022

- -Worked as a full stack software engineer for lowork
- esign ...oct Ethereur -Main Stack is Front end design and Jevelopment & API design, dev bitcoin, smart contract Etherauri, so id ty